<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Devops on Airplane Craft</title>
    <link>https://airplanecraft.github.io/tags/devops/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Devops on Airplane Craft</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:40:37 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://airplanecraft.github.io/tags/devops/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Devops traning</title>
      <link>https://airplanecraft.github.io/posts/devops-traning-slide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2022 10:40:37 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://airplanecraft.github.io/posts/devops-traning-slide/</guid>
      <description>
        
          
            &lt;h1 id=&#34;devops&#34;&gt;Devops&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;p&gt;DevOps is a set of practices that combines software development (Dev) and IT operations (Ops). It aims to shorten the systems development life cycle and provide continuous delivery with high software quality.DevOps is complementary with Agile software development;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;CI/CD is a best practice for devops and agile development. CI/CD bridges the gaps between development and operation activities and teams by enforcing automation in building, testing and deployment of applications. CI/CD services compile the incremental code changes made by developers, then link and package them into software deliverables. Automated tests verify the software functionality, and automated deployment services deliver them to end users. The aim is to increase early defect discovery, increase productivity, and provide faster release cycles. The process contrasts with traditional methods where a collection of software updates were integrated into one large batch before deploying the newer version.&lt;/p&gt;
          
          
        
      </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
